Summary_

I am a Computer Systems Engineering student in my final year at the University of Auckland. In addition to the postgraduate courses I'm currently taking, I tutor Stage 3 and Stage 2 courses so that I can assist students in the years below me to become better programmers and engineers. I first started programming when I was 14 and enjoy spending my extra time working on a variety of projects to improve my current skill-set. I am quite comfortable working and developing in a Linux environment, as I own multiple devices running Arch Linux. Outside of computers, I study Japanese in what time I have left, so that I can experience another culture and widen my view of the world. I also practice Gōjū-Ryū Karate to keep myself fit.

Experience_

Teknique Ltd. Rosedale, Auckland

SOFTWARE ENGINEERING INTERN

Nov 2019 - Feb 2020

Used Docker extensively in creating and managing servers to deliver data visualisation using various propietary software solutions

- · Authored scripts in MySQL and PostgreSQL to generate large quantities of test data for the purposes of data visualisation
- Migrated an in-house quality assurance test suite from Python2 to Python3
- Developed hardware and software tests using an in-house SDK for embedded camera solutions
- Soldered various components for use with an embedded camera solution

University of Auckland Auckland CBD, Auckland

TEACHING ASSISTANT

July 2019 - Present

- Assisted students in learning the fundamentals of Object Oriented Programming in C++
- · Assisted students in learning the fundamentals of Python, such as lists, dictionaries and classes
- Held and managed weekly in-person lab sessions for students to ask questions and seek help

Epsom Girls Grammar School DIGITAL EXAMINATIONS CO-COORDINATOR

Epsom, Auckland

Nov 2017, Nov 2018, Nov 2019

- · Organised and managed the delivery of a digital platform for NCEA exams to over 1000 students over 3 years
- Personally invigilated over 40 exams from NCEA Level 1 through to NCEA Level 3 during my time as an invigilator
- Police certified to work in any high school in New Zealand

Skills

Frameworks CherryPy, .NET Core, React

Languages C, C++, Java, Javascript, MIPS Assembly Language, MySQL, Postgres, Python, Visual Basic, VHDL

Operating Systems Linux, Windows, MacOS **Software** Docker, Git, Grafana, Vim

Education

University of Auckland Auckland CBD, Auckland

B.Eng (Hons) in Computer Systems

Mar 2017 - Nov 2020

Undergraduate degree combining Electrical Engineering and Software Engineering to create a holistic view of computers and their operations.

ACG Parnell College Parnell, Auckland

CAMBRIDGE INTERNATIONAL EXAMINATIONS

Jan 2012 - Dec 2016

Top-achieving student in A-Level Mathematics, Physics, Computer Science and AS English.

Proiects

Portfolio Website GitHub

PERSONAL

UNIVERSITY

Ongoing

Ongoing

- · A portfolio website to showcase the projects I've worked on and provide some basic information to potential employers
- Designed from scratch using a combination of custom components and Material UI's React component library

Roll for Reaction GitHub

- A turn-based rogue-like dungeon-crawler RPG that takes inspiration from *Dungeons and Dragons*
- · Implemented using React and Redux, the game supports both desktop and mobile platforms